Curt Jarzab

Engineering Maintenance Technician

Columbus, OH 43235 maerskman1@gmail.com 708-336-8821

I am seeking a full time position. I am an Engineering Maintenance Technician in a commercial full service hotel in Columbus Ohio. I studied at Environmental Technical Institute in Itasca Illinois Prior to some Air Conditioning course work at the College of Dupage. I have been employed In commercial Maintenance since 2015. I am a strong candidate for the position of Building Engineer at Facebook New Albany Data Center. I am highly dependable, reliable, and resourceful.

I collaborate well with contract technicians regularly with everyone from fire Marshall to HVAC, Electricians, and Plumbers. In past positions I have had the pleasure to contribute in the maintenance of both state of the art cooling Tower air conditioning system as well as currently maintaining a chilled water air conditioning system at a 200+ room full service hotel. I am always seeking to learn something new. As a career minded professional I am a Hardworking Maintenance Engineer.

I have Approx. 10 years Warehousing Shipping & Receiving, Load and Unload, Dock office/ASP (Administrative Support), as well as Information systems dept, and Warehouse Inventory experience. I am a very hard worker and I produce results. As a hobby I like to work with computers especially rebuilding them and have taught myself to code. I am On-time, make it a point to report to work early, and I am very loyal. I look forward to reviewing my qualifications with you soon.

Sincerely,

Curt Jatzab

Work Experience

Engineering maintenance Technician

Embassy Suites by Hilton - Columbus, OH July 2017 to Present

As a maintenance engineering technician, I am responsible for the upkeep and maintenance of the Building systems as well as the grounds. Providing Excellent customer service and resolving issues as they arise. I work on a rotating schedule and maintain HVAC, Pool, Electical, and Plumbing systems as well as carpentry when the need arises.

Engineering Maintenance Technician

The Joseph - Columbus, OH 2016 to 2017

I am an engineering technician on a 3 person team. My excellent customer service is something I take pride in. My primary responsibility is conduct preventative maintenance tasks within the hotel. I cover the chief engineers' schedule when he is out and I cover the part-time man when he is out as well. I am currently learning how to PM the HVAC heat removal system that occupies the entire penthouse. When I am not doing either of those responsibilities I am usually working on other projects around the building. Painting, plumbing, wiring, some punchout work it varies on the day. Many of the projects we have, involve learning how to repair or replace material not seen in your typical hotel. It is a constant learning process but I am mechanically inclined so i am well suited to the job. There is nothing

I cannot learn within reason and I have high expectations for myself. I will be an excellent addition to your winning team.

Maintenance Technician

Fairfield Inn & Suites - Columbus, OH 2015 to 2016

Perform morning grounds inspection duties including pool chemistry, and upkeep. Drywall, painting, plumbing, electrical commercial property maintenance. maintain parts shop in a neat and orderly fashion at all times. Also Function as Airport Shuttle Bus driver on charter shuttles for corporate clients. Knowledgeable fast learner.

Accomplishments

I successfully brought all 135 rooms at current employer to excellent standards as dictated by corporate requirements. I continue to keep rooms to high standard of excellence. Always learning is crucial to be a successful Maintenance Engineer. I seek out new challenges to expand my knowledge in building maintenance. I believe in doing it right the first time. Carpentry, drywall, Electrical, Plumbing, Pool Maintenance, Trade School HVAC. I have learned to fine tune my customer service skills. I am always seeking more knowledge to build my list of skills on.

Attorney retainer svcs

Harvard Risk Mangement - Columbus, OH 2012 to 2015

on Retainers Contracts, Process service subscription, purchase transaction paperwork.

• Contact individuals and companies for decision maker meetings and presentation.

Administrative Support

Warehouse Inventory - Delaware, OH 2009 to 2011

- Inventory, Record, Distribute electronic company assets (Vocollect Talkman A500 Mobile Computing Devices.
- Administer consistent, quality customer service to internal and external Customers
- Receive incoming calls from other departments providing technical advice to Administration staff and management
- Train new associates, Inventory, Data Entry, Problem resolution.
- Asset to the company.
- Accurately Preserve and inventory company assets.
- Coach and support warehouse Associates in implementing company procedures.
- · Compliance of procedures and policies, file reports as needed, Utilize Word, Excel, and Outlook when Required.
- Preserve and Inventory company assets, investigate discrepancies and report utilizing Scan Manager and Microsoft office suite.

Container Yard Coordinator, Administrative

Maersk Group, INC./ Bridge Terminal Transport - Chicago, IL 2006 to 2008

Coordinate In and Outgating Procedures according to company specifications. Mostly container and container chassis inspections checking for violations to the FHWA rules for highway transportation safety regulations. Proper paperwork completion. Utilization of Microsoft Office Suite.

Material Handler

Rehire - Bridgeview, IL 2005 to 2006

Education

Air conditioning

College Of Dupage - Glenn, IL

2008 to 2008

Environmental Technical Institute - Itasca, IL

2007 to 2008

Additional Information

Skills

Warehouse Information Systems, & Inventory

(2 years), Commercial Building Engineering & Maintenance (2 years), HVAC and building maintenance education ETI (Environmental

Technical Institute) (1 year)